从老特区大理石台阶到坦帕海岸日落
From the marble steps of old DC to the sun soaked Tampa coast.
格林德尔社区大学出品
我来  我见  我薇琪
一个女人的独角戏
我去过所有人类出现过的地方
I have been to every place where you can find a human race
可只有我最薇琪
but I have been Vicki the mooooooost!
我去拿个铲子  埋葬已死的戏院
I'm gonna go get a shovel, because theater is dead.
星霸
Hi Starburns.
托德  你不用鬼鬼祟祟地当怪胎
Todd, you know you don't have to creep around to be weird, right?
你野餐时就很怪胎
You're weird at picnics.
听说彩弹大战了吗
Did you hear about the paintball game?
我听说不许打彩弹了
Yeah, I heard there was no paintball.
已经被和谐了
I heard it was banned.
要知道耳听为虚
Well, you can't believe everything you hear.
好吧  你刚问我有没有听说什么
Okay, you just asked if I heard something
又告诉我耳听为虚
and now you're invalidating the whole.
*彩虹  枕头  纸杯蛋糕  天使*
* Rainbows, pillows, cupcakes, angels, *
*伦敦  骏马  手套  可可*
* London, horses, mittens, cocoa, *
*薇琪  亲爱的小薇琪*
* Vicki, dear sweet Vicki, *
*今晚我不会回家...*
* I won't be home tonight... *
*薇琪  你值得更好  更好的*
* Vicki, you deserve more than this, more than this, *
*我会给你钻石与星光*
* I'll give you diamonds and starlight, *
*星光  可我已长眠地下*
* starlight, but I'm dead *
知道我为什么能打败你吗  托德
Do you know why I beat you, Todd?
真的假的  你真不知道
Seriously, you don't?
因为我也不知道  太疯狂了
Cuz I don't either, but that was insane.
我可都五十了
I'm 50, here.
我觉得我今年能赢
I think, I think I could win this year.
我觉得我今年可以一战到底
I think I can go all the way.
可事实是  你将一银即倒
Actually, you'll be settling for silver.
■
本字幕首发于字幕组网站
www.ZiMuZu.tv 欢迎交流
翻  译    别扭大菜弹
翻  译    神隐DayDay
翻  译    吴宇森章鱼
翻  译    缺白鸽子Vie
时 间 轴    苏菲易水寒
后  期    钢铁鱼骨头
顾  问    greydale
校对/总监    夕阳狂奔橙
废柴联盟
第六季  第十一集
告诉我是谁  不然就开除你  很简单
Names, you give me names or you're expelled, that simple.
我说了  我根本不知道有什么秘密彩弹大战
I told ya, I don't know nothing about no secret paintball games.
这是我吸油漆吸嗨了弄上的  我发誓
This is from huffing paint, I swear.
送亚历克斯·奥斯本出学校吧
Escort Alex Osbourne off campus.
等等
Hey, hey, hey!
别那么猴急嘛
Hold your horse panties.
你没跟我说  你知道我本名啊
You didn't tell me you knew my name.
我本想除掉托德的  结果我们俩都被干掉了
Look, I was about to take Todd out, and then we both got shot.
那人简直神出鬼没
Guy was invisible.
一个魂魄
A ghost.
用的是银色彩弹
Uses silver paint.
魂魄
A ghost?
没名字吗
So no name?
我想叫他银魂
I'd call him Silver Ghost,
不过可能已经被某独立漫画
but that's probably already taken
或者什么破龙舌兰酒取过了
by an indie comic book or a terrible tequila.
永别了  星霸
Bye forever Starburns.
不  不要啊  不要  别逼我
No. No. No, no, no, no. No, don't make me.
弗兰
Frankie?
院长  作为领导我尊重您  可要么开除我
Dean, I respect that you are my boss, so either fire me or
要么交给我处理  回你办公室去
let me handle this and go to your office.
替我给你的彩弹兄弟们带个信  杰夫
I want to give your paintball friends a message, Jeff.
早上好
Good morning.
这个时代已经结束
This era is over.
忆往昔彩弹大战乐翻天  看今朝老娘地盘少放肆
It was fun while it lasted, but now mommy's home.
发现携枪者  一律开除
Everybody with a gun will be expelled or fired.
别担心  达特小姐
Don't worry, Miss Dart.
我跟我的弟兄们马上清理完毕
My boys and I will get this cleaned up in no time.
谢谢
Thank you.
杰夫  你记得副校工拉帕里吧
Jeff, do you know Deputy Custodian Lapari.
我们可没什么好印象啊
Oh, we haven't had the pleasure because
因为翁格老师除了用彩弹给我们找麻烦
Mr.Winger has caused me nothing
就没干过什么好事啊
but pain over the years with his paint balling.
抱歉  我已经戒了
I'm sorry. I quit that.
那是陈年旧事了
That's behind me.
那当然了
Sure it is.
清理大粪的工作把他折磨得不轻啊
Handling turds has rubbed off on him.
校工拉帕里这周将在
Custodian Lapari is gonna be honored this week
格林德尔清洁舞会上受到嘉奖
at the Gala for a Cleaner Greendale.
我希望由你来介绍他出场
I'd like you to introduce him.
我为什么要去
Why would I do that?
因为你是格林德尔的真正领导人
Because you're the de facto leader of Greendale.
如果你能发表反对彩弹大战的演说
And if you gave a speech coming out against paintball,
没准可以结束这一切
it might end it.
不  不要  我是没在玩了
No. No. Just because I'm not playing
但也不代表我是那种不让别人玩的小气鬼
doesn't mean I'm the weenie that tells people not to.
拜托了
Please?
就算不是为了格林德尔  就当是为了我
If not for Greendale, then for me?
我会考虑看看
I'll think about it.
我那时候完全不一样
Look, I was a different guy back then.
二  当我没说
Yeah. Two, never mind.
弗兰很不高兴
Well, Frankie's upset.
她是分手了吗
Did she break up with someone?
对方什么性别
Which gender?
我不在乎  不过大家都想知道
I don't care, but everybody else does.
她不高兴是因为彩弹
She's upset about paintball.
彩
Paint?
弹
Ball?
咱们学校不定期地突变成一部致敬惊险动作片
Occasionally our campus erupts into a flawless, post modern,
完美无瑕  充满后现代意味的神话
homage to action adventure mythology,
经常被无知者误认为是拙劣山寨
mischaracterized by the ignorant as parody.
现在弗兰公开声明彩弹大战是违法的
Apparently, now that Frankie's declared it illegal,
所以它已经转入地下
it's gone underground,
在此时此刻依旧在活动中
and is still happening as we speak.
都是新生吧
Well maybe for freshman,
说实话我们都已经玩到极致了  不是吗
but honestly we've kind of done it to death, right?
玩过
Done it?
搞过  我现在也赢过几次了
Nailed it? I've won a few time now.
谁还记那个  逊爆了
No, who keeps track of that? Lame!
我主要考虑的还是弗兰
I'm thinking mostly about Frankie.
她是我们的朋友
She's our friend,
非常在乎这学校  所以我觉得如果被她发现
and she cares about this school, and I think it would
我们中有谁背着她搞破坏  她会伤心至死的
break her heart if she caught any of us undermining her goals.
是啊  没错
Yeah. Yeah.
同意  大家都同意
I agree. A reasonable agreement.
你们俩说的都对
You're both right.
那就散会吧
Well, meeting adjourned, I guess.
这样挺好的
This is good.
很高兴我们都同意不玩了
I'm glad we all agree not to do this.
这样我打败你们就容易多了
Is gonna make it a lot easier for me to beat you.
什么鬼
What the hell?
他们杀了我
They killed meeeeeee!
别干傻事
Don't do anything stupid.
干点傻事
Do something stupid.
我以为我们都不玩了呢
I thought we weren't playing.
-这是联盟吗   -我不知道  是吗
- Is this an alliance? - I don't know, is it?
-谁的人  -别废话了  埃尔罗伊
- Who's people? - Cut the crap, Elroy.
住手   你干嘛呢
Stop that, what are you doing?
回你教室去
Go back to class.
翁格玩彩弹枪了
Winger's playing paintball.
没有  他没有
No, he's not.
想都别想  不许想
Don't think about it, don't think about it.
别轻举妄动
Don't do it.
成熟点吧
Grow up.
你们干嘛呢
What are you doing?
我才不要玩
I'm not playing.
一个不玩的人
For a guy who's not playing,
刚刚身手敏捷地干掉了好几个啊
you sure are shooting a bunch of mothers.
那叫本能
That was instinct.
我就是牛逼到无可救药
I can't help being a bad ass.
可我不玩
But I am not playing.
那我们速战速决吧
Okay, so let's make this painless.
-慢着  -别碰她
- Take it easy. - Leave her alone.
住手
Stop it.
都别闹了
Knock it off.
弗兰马上就来了
Frankie is coming.
你们想想孰轻孰重
What is important to you people?
杰夫·翁格打的我
Jeff Winger shot me.
我得用超声波定位吗
Do I use echo location to navigate?
你都知道你不是蝙蝠了  怎么还问
Why would you ask that after learning you aren't a bat?
你好啊
Hello.
弗兰好
Hi, Frankie.
弗兰
Frankie.
杰夫  刚刚一个学生从我身边跑过
Jeff, student just passed by me
说你用彩弹打了他
and said you shot him with paint.
好吧
Okay.
所以你绝对没有玩彩弹
So, you are definitely not playing paint ball?
没有
No.
弗兰  在此之前我一直挺淡定的
Frankie, I've been cool up until now, but I gotta tell you,
可你对我这么疑神疑鬼的  我很不开心啊
I'm starting to get offended by your suspicion about this.
-好[井]  -井乃渴时地中孔
- Well. - Well is a hole in the ground when you're thirsty.
我跟你说了  我没玩彩弹
Oh. I'm telling you, I ain't playing no paintball.
好吧  大家别介意
Okay, take it easy guys.
不管怎样吧  谢谢你教我
And for what it's worth, thank you for teaching me the cool,
如何高冷地应对别人说「好」这个字
new way to respond to people saying the word well.
大家慢玩
All right guys.
拜  弗兰  慢走
Bye Franks take it easy.
你们别闹了好吗
Would you stop doing that?
玩家无罪
Don't hate the player.
行话先不管  安妮这话是对的
Colloquialisms aside, Annie's right.
今年要恨  就恨这场游戏
The thing to hate this year is the game.
你们愿意来跟我看看吗
Can I show you all something?
这场游戏通过一台在线匿名服务器运行
You know this game is being run anonymously through
但搭建服务器的人是谁呢
an online server, but who set it up?
他们没留下任何线索  这本身就是个大线索
They haven't left a clue which is a really big clue
因为如果他们真的这么无所不能
because if they're this good at anything.
他们何必还来这里
Why are they here?
服务器运营者
Whoever's running this server
给赢家提供了一份巨大的现金奖励
is offering a huge cash prize to the winner.
更加提供了他们不在场的证明
More evidence they don't go here.
而且好像游戏里有他们自己的人
And they seem to have their own man in the game.
你们可能听说过有一个神秘玩家
You've probably heard about a mysterious player
用的是银色彩弹
using silver paint balls.
来看看这些IP地址
Well, look at these IP addresses.
这是跟我想的一样吗
If that means what I think it means,
我们竟然在跟乱码打交道
we're dealing with gibberish.
还我眼镜
Those are mine.
是我们学校里的某个学生或老师
That's a student or teacher on this campus
开了一条加密通道通向校外网站
opening an encrypted tunnel to an off campus site.
有啥了不起  我经常干这事
Big deal. I do that all the time.
我都是攒到周六晚上干
Oh, I save it all up for Saturday night.
没错  是没什么了不起的
You're right, it's no big deal.
但每当有普通玩家被某个未知射手的
Unless you always do it immediately before a paintball player
高级银弹射倒之后  马上就会有人
is taken out with premium grade silver paintballs
连上这个加密通道
by an unknown shooter.
而且连上的必须是这个IP地址
And unless the IP that you're connecting to, is this one.
我就知道
Aah, of course.
所以银弹玩家是什么人
So who's the Silver paintballs guy?
间谍  刺客  佣兵
Spy, assassin, mercenary,
隐匿于我们之中的坏家伙
bad person walking among us
面带微笑  吃吃暗笑
laughing, laughing quietly.
如果被我们看到
And then if we look,
他会假装成好像在看什么搞笑的事
pretending that he was looking at something funny.
我没猜错的话你们都有麻烦了吧
I suppose you all should be in trouble.
但绝望的院长
But Desperate Deans,
但绝望的...
but desperates...
但绝...
but des,
但绝望的院长需要绝妙的对策
but desperate deans call for Deansperate measures.
出自Desperate times call for desperate measures
从现在起  你们都要为我效力
From here on out, you work for me.
你刚才说的正好证明了我的观点
Everything you're saying just proves my point,
唯一输掉比赛的办法就是去玩它
that the only way to lose this game is to play it.
要我说就坦然去玩  还要跟弗兰坦白
And I say we do the honest thing, and tell Frankie.
整个学校已经参战并在不停败北  包括弗兰
The school's playing and losing already, Frankie included.
如果我们中的有人能赢得比赛
If the people in this room play to win,
我们不仅能拿下城市大学的奖金
we can not only take City College's money,
我们还可以揭露银弹玩家
we can expose Silverballs, and,
然后  揭露城市大学  拯救格林德尔
in turn, City College, and save Greendale.
基本上也就是拯救弗兰
Which is basically saving Frankie.
好的  所以我们要保持低调
All right, so we lay low,
并找出银弹玩家的身份
and we try to find out who Silverballs is.
我们没...先说清楚  我们还没投票起名
But we're not, to be clear, we did not vote on that name.
你们不用票决就有一个名字了
Here's a name you don't have to vote on.
你们可以选择「神隐院长力量」「院长男孩」
You just became the Secret Dean Force, The Dean Boys,
「院长特遣队」「他的院长」和「秘密公民」
Task Force Dean, His Dean, Secret People.
我知道里面有「院长」俩字儿
I know the word Dean is in it.
因为每当政客黯然下野
Because when the politicians fail,
每当和平对话不幸瓦解
and the peace talks fall apart.
每当好像一切尽失
When it seems like all is lost,
无人再关心院长  因为弗兰当道
and nobody really needs the Dean anymore because Frankie's here.
这正是需要你们的时刻
That's when you go in.
你们是我受人尊敬的旧时代所留下的最后堡垒
The last bastion of a bygone era when people respected me.
「院长之军一号」
Dean Force One.
如果你想留在这儿  拜托帮忙拿点水来吧
If you're gonna hang around, we could use some water.
好嘞
On it.
「夜店夜店」  一看就是最没戏的夜店
Club Club, the last club I thought I'd ever join.
你的目标是个不起眼的彩弹军火贩子
Your target is a small time paintball munitions dealer.
我们只知道他是个三十多岁的白种男人
All we know is he's a white male over 30
江湖人称「搞笑老爹」
and his street name is Fun Dad.
夜店的亲们  准备好开始
All right is everybody in this club ready
正宗好夜店  正宗好趴体了吗
to party the way they do in clubs?
康纳  别跟比利胡闹了  派对开始啦
Connor stop horsing around with Billy and party.
DJ好像是搞「喵喵豆」的那个人
DJ might be the guy from MeowMeowBeenz.
我们要的是正宗的情报  阿布蒂
We need clean intelligence, Abed.
别加参考资料  不要回电
No references, no call backs.
最新美剧下载
www.ZiMuZu.tv
这位先生不好意思  话筒借一下
Excuse me good sir, if I could have the mic.
各位顾客请注意  派对优惠大促销
Attention shoppers there's a sale on partying in
就在本人的裤子过道
in my pants aisle.
本人裤内的好货都得清出来
Everything in my pants must go.
当然也不是所有的东西啦  你懂的
Well not everything, that doesn't, you know what I.
酷哥
Koogler?
-阿拉丁  -你不是叫「搞笑老爹」吗
- Aladdin. - I thought your name was Fun Dad.
-不是  -这倒简单
- No. - That was easy.
我要买弹药
I need ammunition.
-你是卧底吗  -我凭什么老实回答你
- Are you a narc? - Why would I answer that honestly?
说得好  大多数人也是这样回答的
Good point. It's how most people answer, so.
来吧  怪我问得不好
Yeah, come on, it's a bad question.
主要是卧底实在太多
You just get so many narcs.
别忘了哦
Hey don't forget.
后墙上有张「夜店夜店」夜店的签到表
There's a sign up sheet on the back wall for Club Club Club.
很高兴你这种阿拉伯人会那么喜欢彩弹
Listen, I'm so glad Omar that you're interested in paintball.
我必须跟你说  这里面不能开枪
Now I have to tell you, no shooting in here.
「夜店夜店」头条规矩  这不是搏击俱乐部
The first rule of Club Club is that we are not a fight club.
第二条规矩是  但凡是辣妞
The second rule is that if you're a hot lady,
就得跟本大爷上床
you have to have sex with me.
之后还有一些别的规矩和限制什么的
And then there's a bunch of rules and restriction
都是他们后来又加上去的
that they've just now been adding
因为第二条规矩招来了很多官司
because of the lawsuits based on that, second rule,
我现在不能称它是规矩了
which, I'm not allowed to call a rule.
刚才是我失言了
That was my screw up.
给你看看我的货
Let me show you what I've got here.
好  这些是蓝色旅行者
All right, these are blue travelers.
还有颇具讽刺意味的柠檬黄
I think I've got some sarcastic mellow yellows in here.
这种超赞的  这个是绿色小气鬼
Those are great. And these are green meanies.
一触即爆  可用颜料标记你的目标
They explode on contact, and they mark your target with paint.
所有彩弹都一样吧
That's a description of every paint ball.
很好  你很了解行情嘛
Okay, so you know your stuff.
看来我应该给你点行内折扣
Why don't I give you a pro discount?
我想要点更独特的  比如  银色的
I'm thinking something more exotic, something in silver?
好  行啊  非常好
Yeah, okay, great.
我觉得你这想法很不错
I think that's a great idea, you know?
你还想在游戏里保命吗
You want to stay in the game?
快坦白
Talk.
好吧  这样
Okay, look.
你们如果是卧底的话就不能参赛
If you're a narc, you can't play.
如果你是玩家  你跟我上床换弹药也可以
And if you're playing, I do accept sex for ammo.
不然啤酒也可以
Or beer, right?
但不能用比特币  我相信比特币能用
But not Bitcoin. I mean, I believe in it.
但我更想要稳定的真实货币
I just, I think I feel like I need it to stabilize.
银弹玩家到底是谁
Who is Silver Man?
我的会计
My accountant?
你怎么认识大卫的
Oh, how do you know David?
你知道我在问谁
You know what I mean.
谁跟你买银色彩弹的
Who buys the silver ammo?
如果我告诉你  我绝对会没命
Oh, look, if I tell you that, I'm pretendsies dead.
-酷哥呢  -被他们打死了
- Koogler? - They got him.
挺好的
That's good.
那他就用不着这个了
Then he wont be needing this.
酷哥的拇指U盘其实是个硬件密钥
Koogler's thumb drive is actually a hardware encryption key.
可以解密吗
Hm, can it be unencrypted?
不行  你要用它来解加密的东西
No, you use it to decrypt something encrypted.
用锁锁住的钥匙
A key with a lock on it.
我要对咱们的敌人说一句
I'll give our enemy this.
他们好聪明
They're clever.
我们怎么凑成一对了
Why did they pair us together?
看  酷哥和银弹玩家之间有条信息链
Look, a message chain between Koogler and Silverballs.
他订购了一大批弹药
Now he's ordering a huge batch of ammo,
并强调要赶在格林德尔清洁舞会之前收货
and stressing that he needs it before the Cleaner Greendale Gala.
城市大学要...
City College is...
城市大学要摧毁弗兰的舞会
City College is going to crash Frankie's Gala.
这里就是银弹玩家选购银弹的地方
And here's where Silverballs decides on silver balls.
什么颜色打在海军蓝的连体裤上最酷
Which color will look coolest against a navy blue jumpsuit?
谁会穿连体裤去参加正装舞会啊
Who wears a jumpsuit to a black tie gala?
尊贵的嘉宾
The guest of honor.
你的网速咋这么烂
Is your Internet not working?
一张照片而已  慢的要死啊
It's one photo. It's taking an hour.
居然还得敲一下键盘  真是...过时
You have keystrokes programmed to, eesh, that's dorky.
看来我们要去租正装喽
Looks like we'll be renting formal wear.
我负责量杰夫瑞的尺寸
I'll measure Jeffrey.
翁格先生  你捯饬得不错嘛
Mister Winger, you clean up nice.
您太客气了  我一直这么玉树临风
Oh, come on. I'm always good looking.
这个计划很远大啊
This seems ambitious.
这个空中轻轨更多的是象征了我们的潜力
Well, the monorail is more symbolic of
而并非建造上的可能性
our potential than it is potential,
我们的教学楼永远不会盖成这个样子
and none of our buildings will ever be shaped like this.
但只要我们努力  就能营造出这样的格调
But with a little work, this is how we could feel.
你应该感到骄傲
You should be proud.
谢谢你  杰夫  谢谢你支持我
Thank you, Jeff, for supporting this.
你耳朵上挂那玩意儿干什么
Why is that in your ear?
我是在呼吁关注对亚美尼亚裔美国人的歧视
Oh, I'm raising awareness of Armenian American stereotypes.
贝尔呼叫钟楼  各小队报到
Bale to Belfry. Let's check in.
种族歧视不是已经很受关注了吗
Should stereotypes have their awareness raised? I...
瞧瞧我
Oh, good lord.
又在质疑你了 怎么回事
I'm questioning you again. Why?
放心去飞  勇敢去追吧  你有你可以
Follow your bliss, sir. You've earned it.
基顿呼叫钟楼  我要提醒各位
Keaton to belfry, I need to just all make sure
我们要非常  非常小心
we are very, very careful here.
贝尔回复基顿  你何不做个榜样
Bale to Keaton, why don't you set a good example
把精力都集中在任务上
by keeping your mind on the mission?
再把眼光集中在目标上
And your eyes on the prize.
目标很安全
Prize is secure.
基顿完毕
Keaton out.
威斯特呼叫钟楼
West to belfry.
入口安全
Entrances secure.
基顿呼叫基尔默  汇报情况
Keaton to Kilmer, status.
基尔默报告钟楼  我正在检查一只勺子
Kilmer to Belfry, I'm currently examining a spoon,
只不过我并非在检查这只勺子
only I'm not really examining it.
我以这个动作为掩护
I'm using it as a cover
暗中监视一个行迹可疑的侍者
while watching a somewhat suspicious waiter.
戴德里克·巴德的嗓音呼叫钟楼
Voice of Diedrich Bader to belfry.
我已经检查物管区三遍了
I've checked the custodial wing for the third time.
我现在可以参加任务了吧
Can I come join the mission now?
不行  戴德里克·巴德的嗓音
Negative voice of Diedrich Bader.
继续检查物管区
Continue to check the custodial wing,
然后查看你办公室的内部情况
and then check the parameter of the inside of your office.
那好吧
Okay.
外说一句  不配枪让我觉得很没安全感
And for the record, I feel very vulnerable without a gun.
这曲子听着怎么这么耳熟呢
Ugh, I know that someone plays in this thing.
Daybreak by Michael Haggins
该曲经常被废柴引用或提及
你好啊  院长
Hey there, Dean.
我们得找个校工
We need a custodian.
院长
Dean.
克鲁尼呼叫钟楼  发现持枪小怪一只
Clooney to belfry I've got a bogey with a gun.
您说什么
Excuse me.
我没跟你说话  我在点外卖呢
I wasn't talking to you, I was ordering dinner.
啊你好  请给我来一只带枪小怪
Yes hello can I get a bogey with a gun
不加咸菜  再单点三份枪
no pickles and three orders of gun.
糟了
Damn it.
克鲁尼惊动了小怪  他朝厨房去了
Clooney slooped the bogey, now he's headed for the kitchen.
要撤退吗
Should we go?
不行  我们不知道是不是我们的人
Negative, we don't know it's our man.
基尔默  克鲁尼  不许妄动
Kilmer, Clooney do nothing
除非你们可以做到悄无声息  不动声色
unless you can do it quietly and calmly.
怎么了你
What the hell?
没事  没事
No. Nothing.
你准备好了吗
Are you ready?
当然
Yes.
克鲁尼呼叫基尔默
Clooney to Kilmer.
-什么  -要我进去支援你吗
- What? - Should I come in now?
得了吧  你进来就完了  大手大脚的
No, no you can't ever come in, ever, you're sloppy.
打扰一下  我能和你谈谈吗
Excuse me, can I have a word with you?
谈什么
About what?
有情报称有人正在校园里办彩弹大战
Well, there's been some reports about a paintball game on campus.
没错  厨房这几个小子肯定也参加了
Oh yeah, you better believe the kitchen boys are playing and
今年我们有一个新的制胜战术
this year we got a new winning strategy.
让傻子们自己送上门来
Let the idiots come to you.
真的
Oh really,
布雷塔  赶紧进来吧
oh Britta you can come in now.
对不起
I'm sorry!
作为格林德尔彩色浩劫中
I stand before you one of Greendale's
最穷凶极恶的猎杀者之一
biggest perpetrators of paint related mayhem
我很高兴地向各位宣布
and I am happy to say
我校那种混乱的局面将一去不返
that those days are fully behind our school.
回望那黑暗的岁月
Looking back on those dark days,
我们可以看出  真正的英雄
it's clear that the only heroes
就是留下来清理残局的清洁工和校工
were the janitors and the custodians left to clean up our messes.
怀着巨大的羞耻和诗意的讽刺
So it is with great shame and poetic irony
我将管理创新奖颁给
that I present the Custodial Innovation Award
副校工  拉帕里
to vice Custodian, Lapari.
你们在里面搞什么鬼呢
What the hell are you doing in there?
杰夫  集中精神
Jeff, focus.
你没事吧  哥们
You all right, man?
-挺好  -不是我们要找的人
- Yes. - It wasn't our guy.
刺客不在厨房里
The assassin is not in the kitchen.
真凶仍然在逃
He's still at large.
现在让我们进行下一环节
And now let's all enact
同时我希望能延续这个新传统
what I hope will become a yearly tradition,
戳爆气球环节
the popping of the balloons.
什么
What?
保持冷静  警戒周边
Stay calm, check your zones.
那是谁
Who's that?
哪个
Where?
我没发现什么动静
I don't see anything.
就是他
Him.
抱歉
Sorry.
就是那些校工
It's the custodians.
格林德尔的校工职员
Greendale's custodial staff
正在组织地下彩弹大奖赛
is running the underground paintball tournament
没准还拿了城市学院的钱
probably with City College money.
这些清理格林德尔的人
The people that clean Greendale
才不想要格林德尔变得更干净
don't want a cleaner Greendale,
他们想让格林德尔不敢自力更生
they want Greendale to be afraid of itself
只能依赖他们
and reliant on them.
编的一手好故事啊
Oh, what an exciting story.
编得比杀马兰的电影还悬疑呢
We're got a real life M Night Shamalyan here.
是沙马兰
It's Shyamalan.
不幸的是  和他的烂片一样
Unfortunately, as with his stories
你编的故事一戳就破
I don't anticipate yours holding up.
你捡软柿子捏
Easy target.
谁在那瞎起哄
Who's heckling me?
难怪了  是个阿三
Oh, of course, it's the Indian guy.
我是阿拉伯裔
I'm Arabic.
好吧  随便你怎么说吧
Okay, let's go with that.
总之  你知道疯狂的故事需要什么做支撑吗
Anyway, you know what goes great with crazy stories?
-证据  -你就是证据
- Evidence. - You're the evidence.
归顺我们  说出真相吧
Come back to our side and tell the truth,
揭露城市学院的阴谋
so City College can be exposed.
或者我能离开这里去城市学院上班
Or I could leave and get a job at City College,
至少他们那里的公共电话不会传染疱疹
where their pay phones aren't only herpe-free,
因为它们早就被拆除了
they're actually removed.
你真以为你输了城市学院的奖金
You think City College will take you
他们就会要你
if you lose their paintball prize money?
我不知道你还有多少人在这里埋伏
I don't know how many men you have left in your game,
但如果你们想离开这里  自然越少越好
but if you're leaving this room, it needs to be a small army.
好吧  我同意
Okay. I agree.
安妮小心
Annie look out.
血债血偿
An eye for an eye.
-不  -不
- No! - No!
该死
Dammit!
就剩我们了吗
We're the last ones left?
掩护我
Cover me.
梦想成真了
Oh, dreams do come true!
找到他了  他进了储藏室
Okay, we got him. He went into a supply closet.
看到了  我想对于校工来说
I know. I guess to a custodian,
储藏室就像需要守卫的阵地
a supply closet is like a location.
我心里舒服多了
I'm actually relieved.
我之前以为这会是一场严峻考验
I thought this was gonna be a whole gauntlet.
我对谁输谁赢已经不感兴趣了
My heart was not in it.
我居然还射杀了一个残疾小孩
I mean, I shot a disabled kid.
我可再也不会这样做了
I can't do this anymore.
你在看什么
What are you looking at?
这不是储藏室
This isn't a closet.
校工艺术博物馆
蒸汽管道展览
热烈欢迎你们参观本博物馆
Oh, it's really nice of you guys to visit,
虽然你们并不是特意来参观的
not that you ever would have done it intentionally.
你这些蒸汽管道阻挡不了我们
Your steamy pipes can't stop us.
这个博物馆展览还真是够糟心的
Well, it would be a pretty bad museum exhibit if it could.
放弃吧  拉帕里
Give it up, Lapari.
院长  我有麦克风
Hey Dean, I have a microphone.
你有啤酒
You have a beer.
上帝自有安排
God has a plan.
我有啤酒吗
I have a beer?
这是以前喜剧演员对台下起哄观众的老词儿
It's an old stand up line for using up hecklers.
继续前进
Keep moving.
你演过喜剧脱口秀啊
Did you do stand up?
你是因此才沦落成校工的吗
Is that how you became a custodian?
哥们  90年代那会我也演过
Listen man, I was there in the 90s.
我曾经在开麦夜演过几场
I did a few Open Mic Nights.
完美洁净表面展厅
我见证了卡拉ok的崛起
I saw what Karaoke did.
你真的很不厚道
It wasn't cool man.
院长  你我也没有什么太大的不同
We're not so different, you and I, Dean.
你没发现我们都处在一样的环境下吗
Don't you see we're both in the same situation?
你逗我呢
Oh, you gotta be kidding me.
校工人体模型展厅
去死吧  把他们全都灭了
Screw it. Shoot them all.
其中肯定有他  挨个射击
One of them is him. Shoot every single one.
他不在这后面
He's not back here.
好吧
Okay.
装弹
Reload.
肯定又是拖把斗武桥  木屑大峡谷什么的
Must be a mop jousting bridge over sawdust canyon.
我们都是冲着哺乳动物徒劳咆哮的恐龙
We're both dinosaurs roaring in vain at the mammals.
当你让弗兰·达特来到我们这个世界时
What do you think was gonna happen
你觉得会发生什么呢
when you let Frankie Dart into our world?
在她发现那些最肮脏的东西之前
How much more clean can she make the school
她能把学校变得多干净呢
before she notices the dirtiest thing of all about it.
你以为我是坏人  其实我不是
You think I'm a villain, but I'm not.
我只是在保护一个所有人都能当英雄的地方
I'm defending a place where we all get to be our own heroes.
我们固守在这里是因为我们都无法拥有美好
We're all here because none of us can have nice things.
我还以为你们是假人模特呢
I thought you guys were mannequins!
居然被逆袭了
What a backfire!
奖金的事是真的吗
Is the money real?
不管是谁赢
No mater who wins?
院长  你要干吗
Dean, what are you doing?
你乱想什么呢
What are you thinking about?
我不知道  我不知道
I don't know, I don't know.
他说得对  杰夫瑞
He's right, Jeffrey.
更干净的格林德尔就像是更健康的香烟
A cleaner Greendale is like a healthier cigarette.
对  胡萝卜条
Yes, a carrot stick.
弗兰把我们变成了胡萝卜条
Frankie can make us a carrot stick.
我们明明是烟草
We're tobacco.
不  我们不是烟草
No, we are not tobacco.
我们是小罗伯特·唐尼
We are Robert Downey Jr,
他当年吸毒嗨到爬人家窗户
he was so high he was crawling into people's windows.
而现在他变成了钢铁侠
Now he's Iron Man.
我们如此自毁  是因为我们更想当英雄
We self destruct like this because we'd rather be heroes
而不是反派  更不愿意做废柴
than villains than just kind of sucky people,
我们得付出巨大的努力才能变得不那么废柴
that need to work a lot at getting less sucky.
她会原谅我们的
She will forgive us.
我了解她  我喜欢她
I know her, I like her,
如果她敢炒你俩的鱿鱼  我也不干了
and if she fires either of you, I'll quit.
她不是敌人  她可以帮我们
She's not the enemy, she can help us.
我们只需要冷静下来
We just have to cool it.
他说的都是真的
It's true, what he said.
如果你们都放下枪
If you guys lower your guns,
我不会给你们开派对庆祝
I'm not gonna throw you a party,
但是我也不会解雇你们
but i'm not going to get anyone fired either.
周一见  白痴们
I'll see you Monday, idiots.
那么谁赢了
So who wins?
-我们...  -好吧
- What do we... - Okay,
数到三  我们射击自己的脚自杀
on the count of three we're gonna shoot ourselves in the foot.
一  二
One, two.
咱们周一见吧
I'll see you guys on Monday.
教皇看了看长颈鹿说  我在房间里
And the Pope looks at the giraffe and says I'm in the room.
抱歉这笑话我没完全记清
Sorry I can't remember the whole joke.
没关系  从最后一句听起来挺好笑的
That's okay it sounds very funny based on the last line.
弗兰就要到了  我们准备一下
Frankie's gonna be here soon we should get ready.
我们不是还要这样做吧
We're not seriously still doing this are we?
我们答应过每周做一次  难道要她放弃吗
We promised everyday for a week do we want her to quit?
大家早上好
Good morning everyone.
上次我们进行到哪里了
So, where did we leave off last time?
先生你请说
Yes, sir.
我喜欢大卡车
I like big trucks.
我今天看见了一辆救火车
I saw a fire truck today.
有趣的观点
Interesting point.
还有人想要发表意见吗
Would anyone care to comment?
埃尔罗伊
Elroy?
我放了个臭屁
I made a stinky.
值得深思  下个问题
Worth considering. Next item?
大意面面怎么念呀
How do you pronounce pasketti?
意大利面  还有吗
Spaghetti. What else?
我们能去动物园吗
Can we go to the zoo?
这是一个很重要的问题
Well, that raises a very important point.
我们可以做任何想做的事  只要...
We can do anything we want if,
这非常重要  等你们长大成人就行
and this is very important, if we grow up.
都同意吗
All in favor?
格林德尔社区大学出品
格林和加瑞特
「我来  我见  我薇琪」幸存单口秀
然后她开始把她之前去过的地方唱出来
Then she starts singing about all the places she's been.
可是一共就只有两个地方
Which, by the way, seems to be a total of two.
其中一个是老特区
One of which is old DC.
老特区
Old DC.
薇琪  你是学音乐的  不是历史
Okay fine, Vicki, you're a music major, not a history major.
还有关于她妈妈的梗
And the whole mother thing,
话说她最引以为豪的两件事就是
I mean the two big feathers in her cap are that
她从不为任何东西所改变
she hasn't let anything change her,
这一胜利属于她和绝大多数动物以及所有垃圾
a triumph she shared with most animals, and all dirt,
另外一件事就是她妈死了
and the fact that her mother died,
貌似这是所有妈妈的共同属性
which is like one thing all mother's do.
她是一位好妈妈吗
I mean, was she a good mother?
她集邮吗  她赛车吗
Did she collect stamps? Did she race cars?
我们不知道
We don't know!
我们连她名字都不知道
We don't know her name,
我想如果你问薇琪她妈妈眼睛的颜色
I think if you ask Vicki the color of her mother's eyes,
她会说是死人色
she would say dead.
或者她会说七块钱一个座儿
Or, maybe she would say $7 a seat.
真的不咋地  我跟你们讲
It's bad man, I am telling you.
惨绝人寰啊  无人幸存啊
Nobody is safe, nobody is safe.
蓝色
Blue.
她眼睛是浅浅的蓝色
They were a very pale shade of blue.
抱歉我的表演没有妥当地纪念她
I'm sorry my show didn't honor her memory properly.
我会补偿你的
I'll try to make it up to you.
我们会一起努力的
Actually we both will a, a,
在我们新节目的首演中
at the premier of our new show.
薇琪和加瑞特
Vicki and Garrett.
让我们为薇琪的母亲鼓掌
Let's have a hand for Vicki's mother everybody.
站起来吧  康妮
Stand up Connie.
薇琪的母亲  薇琪的母亲
Vicki's mother, Vicki's mother!
嘘
Boo!
我们倒是希望你们喝倒彩
We'd rather you boo.
这说明你们真的感受到了什么
It means you felt something.
没错  你们可以喝倒彩
That's right. You can boo.
安迪·考夫曼最爱喝倒彩
And, Andy Kaufman loved booing.
说明一下  我们为这场演出做了很多努力
Then again, we did put a fair share of work into this.
你们不要太过分吧
Like, you don't have to be dicks.
■
最新美剧下载请登录字幕组网站
www.ZiMuZu.tv
扫描左边二维码关注我们的微信号
或搜索微信号: ustvboom
非常欢迎爱好者加入字幕组一起翻译海外影视剧
■
你看懂了没
Did you get any of that?